Taco Bell. They they crack me up, right?
Because they just take some other
dessert you're kind of familiar with and
change it a little bit. You know, we
have Cinnabon bites.
Isn't that just a cut up Cinnabon?
I mean, yeah, but we cut it up for you.
Okay. You could say gracias.
A lot of comedians uh after the show, we
get to talk to people. We get to meet
people. They always want to ask the same
questions. The one that I get asked the
most is why do you do standup? How did
you get into doing standup? And it's
pretty simple reason. Um I feel like I'm
funny all the time. And I don't mean 24
hours a day. I mean not just when I'm on
stage, right? But the problem with that
is when I'm funny out there in the real
world and I don't have lights and a
microphone and cameras on me and people
sitting in chairs next to each other
facing me waiting to hear something
funny. A lot of times jokes just go to
waste. So I started doing standup to
give my humor a second chance at life.
A good example of this was the last
Valentine's Day. I was at my local
grocery store in the floral department
trying to find that perfect bouquet to
take home with me. And there's another
gentleman a couple feet away doing the
exact same thing. And he didn't talk to
me, but he was talking to me cuz I was
the only one around. And he was talking
pretty loud. This is what he says. He
goes, "Man, it's crazy how much money
you got to spend on something that's
just going to die." And I was like, "I
know. And you got to buy them flowers."
Now listen people,
I love my wife, but that may be the
funniest thing I have ever said in my
entire life. Okay,
but he wasn't ready for it.
He's like, "Well, good luck with that,
buddy." And he just started to walk
away. I was like, "Dude, that was gold.
It's a good thing I'm on Twitter.
I'm from Cincinnati, Ohio. Uh, which
means I go on terrible Midwest family
vacations every year.
I have no say in where we go. Two years
ago, we went to Amish country. I don't
know if you guys have been to Amish
country, but that place is not fun at
all. Okay. I uh I did not care for You
know what? I didn't like I'll tell you
what I didn't like the people. I didn't
like the people. I I'm sorry if you're
friends with them. I apologize. I just I
found them to be very hypocritical, you
know, cuz they're all We don't believe
in electricity, but we'll use it if we
need to run your Visa card. And I don't
like that attitude. All right. I said,
"You go big or go home, Ezekiel. Don't
plug up.
It's a slippery slope."
He didn't like me. Probably because his
name wasn't Ezekiel, but he looked like
it should have been,
you know.
I couldn't have been that far off is
what I'm trying to say. I think we just
got started on the wrong foot. Okay. Cuz
the only reason I agreed to go in the
first place was if I was allowed to take
pictures that I could put on Facebook.
And the first time I take a picture, I
get scolded by this Amish man. He says,
"Sir, we would appreciate if you're
going to take pictures that you did not
take them of us." And I said, "Why is
that?" He said, "Pictures give us a
sense of pride and we don't like to do
things that make us feel proud." I said,
"You're charging three grand for a
kitchen table without any chairs to go
with it. I'm pretty sure you're proud of
that table." All right.
Not proud. Why don't you tell me for the
fourth time how you put that barn up in
one day? You're not proud? Okay. I'm
just going to go over here and I'll just
let you know that I don't care how good
your pretzels are, I'm not going to be
coming back here to Amish country. And I
left them a scathing Yelp review. I
never heard back from a manager, which
is so typical. But uh
last year we did Gatlinburgg, Tennessee.
Been there? Yeah. Gatlinburg. If you
haven't been, it's an American Indian
word. It means land of the couples that
wear matching airbrush t-shirts. I don't
know if that's accurate, but it's
accurate. Okay. And they always pick the
same design. It's a silhouette of a much
skinnier couple than the people who are
wearing the t-shirts.
And on the shirts that couple, they are
holding hands confidently in love. Their
feet are in the sand. They're underneath
a palm tree. There's a rainbow sunset on
what is clearly the ocean in the
background. Then they write Gatlinburgg
across the top so that you know which of
the islands in the Smoky Mountains that
they visited, right? They're not they're
not smart people, okay?
But it makes for great people watching.
Now, I don't know if you like to people
watch, uh, but, uh, I'm a huge fan. It's
free.
You know, you just sit there with
someone you love and talk about the
folks walking by for a couple hours and
uh, and Gallatinburgg is prime pickings.
I mean, I mean, get your camera ready.
You're going to see someone that you
like enough to want to share them with
others. And uh,
and I'd like to put this out there. If
you ever take pictures when you people
watch, please email them to me because
my buddies and I trade them like they're
baseball cards. It is It's probably the
most fun game I've ever played.
Uh I'll give you a couple tips if you
think you might want to take pictures
when you people watch. Number one, make
sure that the flash and the sound on
your phone are turned off.
I know, sounds like a no-brainer, right
guys? I've been doing this a long time.
I messed up.
I'm in line for security at the airport.
I'm going this way. Coming at me,
gentleman. Hawaiian shirt, shaved face,
but out of the top of his shirt was this
perm. I don't know if that's the right
a tufted.
It was the brightest, whitest, bushiest
chest hair I have ever seen in my life.
I've seen white chest hair. Okay, this
was next level. It was teased, possibly
bleached.
He looked like a Build-a-Bear whose neck
had been slit to send a message to the
other Build-A-Bears to get it together
cuz the numbers are low, right?
And I knew if I didn't get a picture of
him, I wasn't going to be able to sleep
that night. Now,
here's the rub.
I can't take a picture from this
distance, at this angle. No one's going
to appreciate how awesome this thing is.
If I really want the likes, I got to
time it so that when he's passing by me,
I can get that profile shot,
right? Really give it some depth.
Now, to do this, it's a timing thing.
So, I have this face I make, which is
basically what I'm just checking
Twitter, even though my phone's kind of
pointed in your general direction.
He stops right here. I hit the button.
It's like, can you kick Flash? I was
like,
there's a Pokemon on your shoulder, sir.
Could you please
I'm going to get it. Please hold still.
Oh, he jumped into your obnoxious chest
hair. That stinks. Maybe next time.
We'll get him next time.
We'll get him at the layover.
So, be careful.
The other tip is also a very uh obvious
one, but it's what happened to me when I
was in Gatlinburg, and that's to make
sure you have a full battery. All right.
If you're going to spend a day, people
watching picture taken, charge up
because I'm in Gatlinburg. I'm on the
main drag. If you've never been there,
Gatlinburg is basically just one hill.
It's just just one street, you know,
with museums. Um, I mean, that's their
word, not mine.
I mean, call me oldfashioned, but I just
feel like if Cter, the tow truck driver
from the Dukes of Hazard, is the only
face I can see on the front of your
building, you're not allowed to call it
a museum. Okay? I don't care what's
inside.
They got a lot of gift shops. And then
my favorite place that people watch in
any tourist town, but especially
Gatlinburg, is the old-fashioned candy
kitchen. I love that place so much cuz
no matter what time of day you walk up,
you're going to see the same thing.
There's going to be a hillbilly pressed
up against the window who cannot figure
out how they're making taffy on the
other side of the window, and it is the
greatest thing they've ever seen.
They're like, "Get out of here." Nuh-uh.
Hey, come look.
IT'S WHERE THEY make it.
THE TAFFY FROM CRACKER BARREL. YEAH, IT
ALL COMES from
I don't know how they do it even though
I can see the whole process from right
here. Just stand there hours.
And I saw her a block away, dude. The
Mickey Manel rookie card of people
watching. And I got so excited. I was
like, I've heard about you.
Oh, you are coming home with me.
Easy girl.
Easy girl. I'm not going to hurt you.
I got close enough. I press the button.
Nothing happened. I just press it again.
DEAD BATTERY SIGN. WHAT? NO. I scared
her. She ran back into Ripley's. Believe
it or not.
Believe it or not.
And I just sat down on the bench right
there in between the Pancake Pantry and
Fanny Farles Arcade. I was so mad.
All this time I tracked her. I just let
her get away.
Wish I could pass my phone around, let
you guys see how awesome she was, but I
can't cuz I was careless.
So, I'll just describe her as best I
can.
She had early 1990s hair.
>> Remember that look? Pulled back tight in
a ponytail, but in the front,
>> guys. You remember that look? I don't
know if you ever saw how those got made.
I showed up too early for prom one year.
Haven't slept a full night since. That
haunts me.
I'll never forget. I walked through the
back door, cor hands. She's just
standing there in front of the big
mirror.
She was gorgeous.
But this lady in Gatlinburg, I don't
know how else to descri. She looked like
someone who might frequent a Long John
Silvers/ Kentucky Fried Chicken, like a
twoin- one fast food restaurant. I don't
know if you guys ever go to those, but
there's good people watching in there,
too. Um,
any of them. I don't care what the combo
is. For some reason, the average redneck
brain can't seem to process that there
are two businesses operating behind one
counter and sharing the menu above. And
the first time they see it, it just
catches them off guard. They're like,
"Okay, could I get a
Okay, do I need to be at this register
if I want chicken? I just Is this like a
food court or something?
It's the same company. I can order off
of both of them. Oh, I didn't know that.
Oh, well, I'm getting a family meal
deal. I get two sides. Could I get a
side from this side and then a side from
that side? Like, if I could hurry up and
decide, could I go from side to side for
my sides?
I can. I want to try that. Okay. Um,
well, extra biscuits. I mean, I knew
that before I came in here. And
what does Long John Silvers have? Hush
puppies. What? Can I do that? Two
breaths. Oh, yeah. Hook it up.
I know it sounds like I'm really
exaggerating for the sake of standup
comedy, but it's not as much as you
think. Okay,
I promise if you go to any twoin-one
fast food restaurant and just grab a
seat close to the register, just within
earshot, within 5 minutes, you'll hear
some trucker spit out a sentence that
has never been formed in the history of
words cuz he's buckling under the
pressure of the line that's now formed
behind him. He's like, "Oh god, I'm
sorry, you guys. I just I hadn't even
thought about tacos." And then I come in
here and boom, right there they are next
to the pizza.
But if you can make wherever you go half
of it Long John Silvers, like that's
where you're going to have the best
time. All right.
At any Long John Silvers, you will hear
a grown man ask for extra crumbs, which
is a new low for our society
and really racist humans. Now, if I've
completely lost you, Long John Silvers,
it's a fast food seafood restaurant. And
what they do is is they take chicken and
fish and they dip it in their batter and
then they put it in the deep fryer. And
when they flip it from the deep fryer,
little pieces of that batter break off.
And then a pile of those little pieces
form. And then people go, "Hey, could I
get a scoop of the thing that right
there? I want some of that stuff." Like
the garbage on the bottom. I want some
of like put some of that into my
treasure chest.
They get all And I was like, "Did that
guy just ask for more crumbs?" Like I
thought I might have misheard, right?
She pushes a button on the register.
Boop. Crumbs. 10 cents. I was like, "You
got to be kidding me. How often does
this happen?" Okay, seriously.
Like, I thought I could be witnessing
the first time in the history of Long
John Silvers where some guy was like,
"Listen, this is going to sound a little
crazy, but I'm a little short on cash
and I have a long drive ahead of me.
Could you maybe just put some of that
stuff into a cup? I could snack on it
while I'm on the road. I don't know."
No, people, it happens so much that it
has been programmed into the register.
And if that's the case, right, if
whatever you call that stuff has its own
button,
>> which I'm pretty sure we can all agree
was not in the original business plan,
that tells me that there was a day
somewhere that it went down, right?
And as a professional people watcher,
I'm just mad I wasn't there to see it,
you know, cuz I just picture some
toothless manager storming out of the
back. Hey, SOMEBODY'S GOING TO HAVE TO
START PAYING for these crunchies. All
right, I can't be giving this stuff away
all day if everybody's going to ask for
it. We got to figure something out.
Let's just be honest. Y'all love free
stuff. That's what it is, ain't it?
Yeah, it is. That's why we had to get
rid of our tartar sauce pump and switch
to packets. Put them behind the counter.
Limit two per customer cuz y'all were
pumping it right into your boats. Are
you kidding me? NOBODY NEEDS THAT MUCH
TARTAR SAUCE.
and I'm sick of dealing with it. And he
tries to slam the door, but it's that
metal kitchen door, right? So, just
10 minutes later, no one's speaking cuz
you can still hear him in the back
ticked off. I ain't settling down,
Tommy. I'm sick of this. They don't pay
me enough to put up with this. I'm so
mad. My hand's shaking. I'm supposed to
bowl tonight. Now what?
I'm done. Well, I don't care if I said
it before. I mean it this time. You
watch. Soon as I can afford that lift
kit and them Luke Bryant tickets, you
ain't never going to see me again. I'm
out.
Well, of course I'm going. Florida,
Georgia lines opening. I ain't going to
miss that.
They're the only dudes that can settle
me down right now.
You do that for me.
All right, you take the Nelly part.
You make me want to roll my
Okay, listen.
Obviously, I've thought way too much
about a day that probably never
happened. Okay, I'll give you that.
But I have questions and I want them
answered. And the only people that can
answer them are those in charge at the
Yum Brands. If you're not familiar with
who they are, Pizza Hut, Taco Bell,
Kentucky Fried Chicken, Long John
Silvers, A&W root beer. Now, I don't
know what they're on,
but they're on something, okay? All
their ideas, whether it's for the
restaurant, the twoin- one fast food
concept itself, I feel like they just
get together in a big room. Hey, hey,
Carl, you got anything? Um,
there have been several occasions where
I was like, I want fried chicken and
pizza at the same time, but
probably was not in a in a a stable
position to drive two separate places.
Can we do something about that?
Yeah, I think we could do something
about that. We could probably sell both
of those here, right? Yeah. All right,
we can put that down. Save some money on
rent. Phil, what do you guys got? Okay,
we're representing Pizza Hut and um you
know the doughy part around the outside
of the pizza, the crust. The crust,
dude, I told you it was called a crust.
What if
and I'm just spitballing here. We remove
the crust and replace it with a ring of
soft pretzel pigs in a blanket. And if
we can't do that, could we just fill it
with cheese?
Well, we can certainly look into one of
those. If not all of them, I think those
are all good ideas. our audience would
certainly enjoy. Uh Ricky, what about
you? I've always wanted to make taco
shells out of Doritos. That's what I'm
talking about. That needs to be Put that
down first. We got to figure that one
out first. Maybe the greatest idea
that's ever come out of these summits.
We'll start with nacho cheese. Cool
ranch in the fourth quarter. People love
little red and green flexcks on their
taco shells at Christmas. I love it. I
love everything I'm hearing.
Taco Bell, they they crack me up, right?
Because they know if you're going to eat
there, you're going to eat there, right?
Nobody's on the fence about Taco Bell.
Nobody's like, "Well, let's just wait
and see what the next commercial looks
like." You know, if you're going to go
back or not. And Taco Bell knows that.
That's why they can put out a product
that has the exact same ingredients as
three other products on their current
menu. They just change the name and/or
shape of it.
And we'll make you feel dumb for asking
about it.
They're like, "What we have for the
spring?" This is seasoned steak,
lettuce, cheese, tomato, and sour cream
encased in a flour tortilla. Anybody
have any questions? Um, yeah, that
sounds like a steak burrito. Well, it's
not. Okay. A steak burrito is rolled up.
Okay. With this, we fold the sides in.
We press it with a t-shirt iron. I don't
know what's so hard to understand about
the technology we've invested in the
crunch wrap. So, what are we calling it?
It's a It's a crunch right
their desserts. They don't even try with
their desserts. They just take some
other dessert you're kind of familiar
with and change it a little bit. You
know, we have Cinnabon bites.
Isn't that just a cut up Cinnabon?
I mean, yeah, but we cut it up for you.
Okay, you could say gracias.
We took the time to put it into this
drink cup that was already sitting right
here.
How much of the lifting do we have to
do?
I remember a couple years ago the
Hostess company went bankrupt and then
like a month later some mysterious
entity saved them from bankruptcy. I
thought for sure it was Taco Bell. I was
waiting for that commercial
for years. I was waiting for that
commercial. Right. Just it's a Twinkie
burrito. We have stuffed a Twinkie full
of taco meat. Deep fried it.
Sir, would you like Twinkie cream or
sour cream? I don't care if it's coffee
cream. I would like my Twinkie burrito,
some fire sauce, two ho ho loopas,
and a Mountain Dew. The blue Mountain
Dew, too. I want the Baja.
Guys, we got an obesity problem in this
country. And I know you're like, "Is
this dude about to make fun of fat
people while using his stomach as an
armrest?"
And the answer is yes.
I sure am. Okay, you don't have to clap.
It's not supposed to be the funniest
thing I've said so far. Okay.
I understand where I'm at with this
body, right?
There's so many little signs that tell
you you need to you need to fix it. All
right? You need to get get it together.
Like I'm in a way now where if I raise
my hand higher than this, I got to fix
my clothes when I put it right down.
Little signs. Little signs let you know
it's time to clean it up.
had another one recently when I was on a
airplane and the Delta flight attendant
asked me to switch seats to balance out
a 747. That will ruin your day
instantly.
And I know it wasn't me. All right? I
know it wasn't me. It was where I was
sitting versus where there were too many
empty seats. But when you're a little
self-conscious about your weight, you
can't process that. You can't
rationalize. That's not what you hear.
What you hear is, "Uh, sir, if you go 10
ft that way, the whole plane will fly
properly. Could you help us out? Could
you help us out?" Thank you. Thank you.
It's very kind. And if you have to use
the restroom, please ring your call
button so we can send two people back to
your seat. I don't want this. I don't
want to go nose up right into the sun.
Okay. Got it.
>> Yes. I'll give you some extra Biscoff
cookies for this hassle. Yes, I will. I
know they're your favorite. Yes.
I don't know. I think this is going to
my might be my year to get it back. You
guys,
that wasn't supposed to be funny either,
man.
I'm a little optimistic. My weight's
gone up and down my entire life, and I
blame the Booket program. Um,
some of you know, if you're unfamiliar,
when I was in elementary school, Pizza
Hut decided
that the best way to solve the
illiteracy problem was to offer children
a free personal pan pizza if they read
four books or told their teacher that
they read four books. And
and it was great. It was great. When you
were a kid, you got pizza for doing
homework.
But 25 years later, nobody's making you
read books. You're hooked on pizza.
That's kind of what I'm going through
right now.
I just love food. And it's not that I
eat too much. I just eat the wrong
things. I love bad food, you know. But I
know I'm not the only one. I mean, Bath
& Body Works was selling a candle that
smells like mashed potatoes. How fat are
you? Okay. When you want your bedroom to
smell
like buttered mashed potatoes,
this fat. I got the gravy one, too, you
guys. It smelled so good. I'm not going
to lie. I can't lie to you. You're so
nice. It smelled just like them. It was
buy one get one.
And I got a free bottle of fried chicken
body wash cuz I opened up a credit card
to pay for it. Like, it was totally a
good deal.
I mean, you can turn on the TV and know
how we feel about food. There's a reason
there's not a show called Gluten-Free
Vegan Cupcake Wars. No one wants to
watch it.
Nobody's like, "Hey, did you see Salad
Boss last night?" Yeah.
Crazy.
And vegans. I don't know if there's any
vegans in here with enough strength to
raise your hand. Is there one? So, was
that her? Was that someone calling out
for meat? Help. I'm a thing. Help me.
I need a burger.
I'm envious of vegans. If you can do it,
good for you. I ain't about that life.
I've had one vegan experience. It did
not go well. I'm in Jacksonville,
Florida. I'm walking down the street. I
pass a bakery with all these beautiful
things in the window. So, I just kind of
poke my head in. And I go, "Excuse me,
ma'am. What are those on the bottom?"
She says, "That's a root beer float
donut, and it just came out of the oven
about 20 minutes ago. Do you want one?"
I was like, "No, I want two." But
only put one in the bag cuz the other
one ain't making it out of this store.
So, she hands me the one over the
counter. I take a bite as we walk to the
register and I was like,
She's like, "Sir, did you know this is a
vegan bakery?" I was like, "Nope." And
she's like, "Yep, that's what I
figured."
She goes, "See this sign right here? It
says, "No product contains an ingredient
that comes from an animal." And I was
like, "Well, that's ironic cuz this is
some bullshit." No, listen. I didn't say
it. I didn't say it, but I should have
cuz she deserved to hear it. And you do
deserve to hear it. She should have
known when I came through that door that
I was in the wrong place. Look at me.
Look at me.
I guarantee I don't look like any of her
regulars. Okay?
And I would have had a lot more respect
for her if she would have been like,
"Uh, sir, I think you might want the
place down the street." Yeah, that's
okay. It happens all the time. It's
right down the street. Love everything
you're looking for. Milk, eggs, butter,
taste. Right down the street. Just Yeah,
I don't know. Maybe two blocks. I'm sure
you'll call an Uber and you can wait in
here. I know it's at least 70° with no
humidity outside. I wouldn't want you
melting.
All I'm saying is I don't know who came
up with that phrase, looks can be
deceiving,
but I bet they just walked out of a
vegan bakery. That's what I'm trying to
say.
I think you can tell how much we love
food based on the shows that are
popular. You know, Man Versus Food.
They're on round two of that. They got a
new guy cuz the first one exploded or
whatever. Like, do we need to do that
show again? I don't think we do. Do we
not learn the first time around? I did.
I learned what'll happen to your body if
you eat terrible every day for 6 years.
And if you think I'm wrong, watch an
episode from season 1 of Man Versus
Food. Then immediately watch an episode
from season 6 of Man Versus Food. You'll
see the difference. That guy was way
skinnier when he started. And he had an
amazing vocabulary. Where'd that go?
Watch season one. The guy is super
articulate. He's like, "Folks, there is
a symphony of flavor going on in my
mouth right now. When I crunch down, I
got heat from the peppers. I got sweet
from the relish, the salt, and the
bacon. This place is amazing. They've
made perfect harmony in the form of a
sandwich."
But then 6 years later, he's like
This is yummy.
This is so good.
I think it's too easy to eat terrible.
That's what I think it is, you know, cuz
it wasn't that long ago where it's like
you want to eat bad, you got a couple
places you can go to. Now they compete
with each other to see who can offer
something worse for you. Wendy's has a
sandwich called Son of Baconator. Their
food is having kids when they're closed.
Do you understand how bad that is for
you?
That's how I order, too. I'm like, "Uh,
give me a baconator and one of his
children." I don't know. You got a boy.
They're They usually taste better.
Golden Corral is a thing. You can go
there once.
You can't go twice.
cuz there's no way to not look at other
people eating there.
There's no regulations on what people
are and aren't allowed to do with their
food. And that's why it's I'm out.
It's like, no, I understand the value of
giving me access to this chocolate
fondue fountain for $8. But I'm not
going to use it cuz I just saw that guy
passed by with his prime rib.
Hey, that's not gravy. Oh, I know.
What's that? It's whipped cream on corn
on the cob. It's called cream corn. All
right. I'm trying to have lunch. You
don't mind?
You can order bad food off of TV. QVC
sells food. The shopping channel. They
have food on there. You can have four
dozen individually wrapped frosted sugar
cookies delivered to your front door.
They'll give you 6 months to pay it off.
That blows my mind that that's an
option. Why is that an option?
You know what I'm saying? Like, I get
it. If you're buying a laptop or living
room set, sure. But if you have to put
cookies on easy pay, maybe don't get the
cookies. Okay.
And then the next channel over tells you
how to get rock hard abs in 90 days. I
fell for that one, too. P90X.
I got it.
It's a 90-day program. I made it 15
minutes. About 15 minutes.
This is hard.
Nobody on those DVDs look like me. Once
again, that should have been my clue
that I was in the wrong place.
Every person on there yelling at me like
they know me, telling me to keep going
no matter how much it burns. Well, you
look like you've been doing it since you
could walk. How about just one guy that
looks like me laying on the ground out
of breath before the warm-up's over. You
know what I'm saying? I might check out
disc 2 just to see what happened to that
guy.
They're like, "Well, we lost Kevin
yesterday, but we're glad that you're
back."
Cuz today is all about that core.
I don't know. It just wasn't for me.
And I'm sure you're like, "Well, you
probably had a bad attitude about it."
No, I didn't. I had the right attitude.
I upgraded to the multicolored
resistance bands.
I expedited the shipping.
I wasn't even looking for it. I'm just
on the couch minding my own business,
watching TV. This dude comes on. He's
like, "Hey, man. You want a six-pack?"
Yeah.
You want in 6 months?
I mean, three would be better.
Done.
So I called him, put it in, and within
seconds immediately regretted every
decision I had ever made in my life that
led me up to that moment
cuz I was terrible at it right from the
beginning. And I think that's why I got
so frustrated, you know, cuz like let's
say this is where my health was and I
see the P90X DVD. I'm like, that's it.
That's going to be my ticket. I'm about
to get jacked up.
But I was so bad at it that when I took
it out, I didn't want to do anything. I
just sat around watching TV eating
Oreos. I tried every kind of Oreo they
came out with almost out of spite. Like
I was trying to hurt P90X's feelings.
You know when you see your ex when
you're with your new one, you're like,
"This is who I'm with now." That's how I
was a P90X, just eating Oreos right in
their face. How you like that, Tony?
And by the time I snapped out of that
funk and I felt like I wanted to be
active again, I was down here. I was
like, "Dude, this is not fair. I'm
fatter because I tried P90X."
And that's how it went with everything.
diets. I tried every kind of diet. I was
on this Minecraft diet. Three square
meals a day. Did nothing.
Exercise programs, gym memberships. I
bought the Fitbit. Everybody was like,
Josh, that's what you need is a Fitbit
technology. You can track your progress
right from your phone. You'll love it.
Got the nicest Fitbit they make.
Vibrates, sends you little messages.
I've just learned to ignore it like
everything else that's ever tried to
help me live a longer, happier life.
Be like, "Want to go for a walk?"
No, I'm good.
What I need is a Quitbit. That's what I
need. I need someone to invent that.
Just a device that'll buzz and send me
little messages that reaffirm this
lifestyle I've grown to love.
You're doing great. Go back to bed. Oh,
okay.
Who wants some meatballs? I want
meatballs.
They're on QVC right now. Oh, okay. And
they were I'm loaded up on meatballs for
2 years. I'll have them paid off in
February. It's great.
What I realized is that I was watching
P90X in the first place. Like that was
what was doing me wrong. Cuz if you
watch it long enough, you're like,
"Everybody looks like this." You know?
But now what I do is when it comes on, I
turn it off and I put on Train Wreck TV
to remind myself there's a lot of people
out there way worse off than I am. So if
I can just maintain this, I'm cool with
that. That's the way to do it. Like it's
so much easier to achieve your goals
when you don't set any. Like seriously,
you just wake up, feel like I've won the
day.
I was watching those shows already. I
was just watching them wrong.
Intervention, Freaky Eaters, I didn't
know I was pregnant. All those shows.
I used to think they were sad. Now I
think they're great for building
self-esteem.
And I understand some people have a
problem with that. I'm just telling you
what works for me. Cuz sometimes I'll be
sitting in my hotel and I'll think, I
don't know if I'm going to have a good
show tonight. And then I turn on My
Strange Addiction. I'm like, yes, I am
going to have a good show tonight. And I
know I am because I'm not going to go
out and eat toilet paper when it's over.
That's how I know.
I don't know if you watch my strange
addiction, but I have a strange
addiction for that show. I'm kind of
obsessed with it. It's fantastic.
Every episode is pretty much the same.
There's a woman eating or drinking
something no human is supposed to
consume.
And then there's a guy doing kind of
creepy stuff.
One lady, my favorite is this one lady
who eats couch cushions. She opens up
the pillows on her couch and then eats
the stuffing out of them. And my
favorite part about her is when she's
done, she immediately zips it back up
like she's trying to keep the rest of it
fresh for later, right? Like get the
hair out. Zip chip clip. So funny. So
funny.
All those shows are on the Learning
Channel. It's hilarious to me. So funny.
We have 700 stations. One of them. It's
called the Learning Channel. That's
where you put those shows.
What are you trying to teach me? Cuz
I'll tell you what, the only thing I've
learned from watching the Learning
Channel, there's crazy people
everywhere. And that's accurate. I don't
care what part of town you live in.
There are crazy people close by you.
And if you ever want to meet them, just
see what they're like. It's super easy.
Have a garage sale. It's all you do.
Put it on Craigslist and in the paper
that you're having a garage sale and a
freak show will form on your lawn
2 hours before the garage sale is even
scheduled to begin.
I'm looking through the blinds. I was
like, "We said 10, right?
Well, they're here.
Look like the Walking Dead out there.
Brains.
No, that says Bargains.
I don't know if you've had a garage sale
and you know what I'm talking about. But
it makes me hate people. I'm not going
to lie to you. It really bothers me. I
don't know why I do it all the every
year, but Cuz those people I just talked
about, they're a real thing. There's a
term for them in the garage sale
community. They're called early birds.
And apparently I'm a jerk cuz I didn't
put in the ad. They weren't supposed to
be there.
This ladyy's just standing out there. I
was like, "Can I help you, ma'am?" She's
like, "Well, I'm here for the garage
sale." I'm like, "Well, you're about 2
hours early." Well, it didn't say no
early birds.
This is how bad it got. This is not a
joke. Last time we had a garage sale.
Press the button to open the door. There
was a woman crouched down who raised up
with the garage door like she's in a
'90s boy band video just kind of
stepping in. I was like, "Get out of
here.
No, this is not Black Friday. There is
nothing in here worth the effort you are
exerting right now.
I get so mad."
Same characters, just different faces.
I'll tell you who the worst one is. guy
who just watched three episodes of
American Pickers and now thinks he's
Indiana Jones. This guy
every time just walks right up. Hey man,
you got any antiques? No, sir. I'm 35. I
don't know why you thought this was the
place to begin a treasure hunt.
But here's the problem. No matter how
annoyed you get, you got to be nice to
him. You can't say whatever you want.
That's hard for me to do. Do you
understand?
I'm like, "No, sir. There's no antiques,
but uh there's some great deals.
This toaster, check this out. We got
married last year. We don't need two
toasters. So, we're selling this one and
it's a dollar and they'll talk you down.
Doesn't matter how good your pricing is.
If they've seen an episode of Pawn
Stars, it's negotiating time. Now, he's
sweating over my toaster for half an
hour. Oh, buddy. I don't know.
I mean, I need a toaster. And that's a
What's that? It's a sunbeam.
I mean, it's all right. You know, it
ain't like a KitchenAid or Hamilton
Beach. You know, something I might get
excited about.
Trying to find one of them Oster
toasters. Anybody around here one of
them? A stainless steel double wide
chamber? That thing will burn a frozen
bagel in 12 seconds. That thing's bad.
This I mean, what am I going to do with
this? Make toast?
Well, the springs are still good.
What' you say? A dollar.
Oh, man.
I'd like to do business with you, but I
mean, we're just so far apart right now.
I don't know.
I mean, I could probably What's today?
Wednesday.
It's going to be tough, but
I mean I could
I could probably go 25 cents. 25 cents.
I'll beat it over your face for free.
How about that, buddy? Cuz let me tell
you something. Watching you leave with a
broken nose will be worth way more than
a dollar at this point. It's a dollar,
sir. It's a toaster THAT STILL WORKS FOR
A DOLLAR. NO. SCREW THIS GUY, HONEY. I
got
I got thrown out of my own garage sale.
She made me leave,
but I couldn't just go. I was like, "All
right, I'm leaving."
But I want everybody to know something.
I will not be disrespected in my own
garage. And because of how all you're
acting, I'm taking the toaster
and the beanie baby with the mystery
stain.
and the PlayStation one without any
games, controllers, or a power cord and
a lid that does have to be taped closed
when you want to use it. That's right.
They're all coming back inside. And I
carried them back into the house along
with my pride.
And the next day, the very next day
as I drove that stuff to Goodwill where
I would lose money and the gas that it
took to get it there,
I got on the phone with my manager. I
said, "Book me for a special on Vid
Angel because I got some stuff I need to
get off my chest." So, thank you guys
for listening. I hope you had a good
time. We'll see you then.